{
    "subject": "resource/Broadminded_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film 'Broadminded' is American films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7444692254066467,
            "question": "Is 'Broadminded' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701875627040863,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Broadminded' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6791278123855591,
            "question": "Who directed 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750096082687378,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Broadminded' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5997971296310425,
            "question": "What country are 'Broadminded' films from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4786740839481354,
            "question": "What themes are explored in 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4025365114212036,
            "question": "When was 'Broadminded' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3489528000354767,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33455032110214233,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2381960153579712,
            "question": "Has 'Broadminded' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film 'Broadminded' is American films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_234_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch 'Broadminded'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_234_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in 'Broadminded'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_234_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'Broadminded' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_234_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_234_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss various aspects of the 1931 film \"Broadminded,\" including its production, cast, and content. Given that it explicitly mentions this as an American pre-Code comedy film from 1931, the statement that \"the subject of the film 'Broadminded' is American films\" is supported by the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The film 'Broadminded' is an American Pre-Code comedy, but it does not specify that it belongs to the genre of American films as a whole. It can be classified under the genre of Pre-Code comedy and American films individually.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The film \"Broadminded\" is an American pre-Code comedy film directed by Mervyn LeRoy, which implies that the subject of the film is indeed American films. However, I inferred this based on the context information you provided, not directly from the statement itself, but since it's part of my evaluation, the fact that 'The subject of the film 'Broadminded' is American films.' is actually correct as per the context information given to me",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}